I've made over $10 million as a personal
trainer, but if I was starting over in
2025, I'd do things very differently.
And this isn't about being rich, this
is about making a good living,
taking care of
your family,
and maybe the luxury of laying down on
your next
flying holiday.
So I'm going to show you everything in
this video that you would
need to go from zero to $1 million.
Now let's begin with stage number one.
This is going to be from zero to $5,000 a
month.
A lot of you won't want to hear this,
but you're going to do the majority of
this
in person. To the side here,
I'm going to set some benchmarks that
are very
important in stage one. Zero to 100 posts,
from zero to 100
hours, from zero to 10 clients,
from zero to 100 followers,
from zero to 100 email subscribers,
and from zero to 1,000 hours.
Now,
I know that can seem quite overwhelming.
I'm just going to go through each one of
those metrics and explain its importance
for stage one.
Let's begin with zero to 100 posts.
Even though you're new to this,
let's get out the gates.
Some important things to think about.
No one really cares about you.
They don't care about your lunch.
They don't care about your workout.
They care about themselves,
and in each person's life,
they have a set of problems.
Now you, in the line of work you are,
can help a lot of people with those using
your expertise, your experiences,
and your knowledge.
Then the fourth thing isn't actually any
of those.
It's the fact that we
are much more inclined to listen to a
stranger.
We are much more inclined to lift more
and heavier weights when people are
watching.
We are much more inclined to work to avoid
a loss, so when we financially
pay someone to do something,
we're more likely to do it.
So let's not forget number four.